<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>BeyondThePines Blog Entries</title>
        <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs</link>
        <item>
            <title>Spring/Summer 2025 Fashion Report: A Comprehensive Runway Breakdown</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/ss25-fashion-month-report</link>
            <description/>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Shawn Mendes Album, New Kylie Minogue, and More Music Still On The Way This Month</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/october-2024-new-music-releases</link>
            <description>Following Charli XCX’s third “Brat” installation, Shawn Mendes returns from a five-year hiatus, and former Little Mix’s JADE releases a solo single.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Artist Sean Ellmore Talks Painting Pop Culture, Wallpapering Miley Cyrus’s Glam Room, and More</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sean-ellmore-interview</link>
            <description>How the L.A. influencer turned your favorite artist's favorite artist went from creating fan art to wallpapering celebrity homes.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>9 Highly Anticipated Films Coming This October</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/october-2024-new-film-releases</link>
            <description>Lady Gaga unveils a secret music project for her part in “Joker: Folie à Deux” while Andrew Garfield and Florence Pugh co-star in fall’s most heartfelt romance.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Unpacking 2024’s Biggest Fashion Trends Through A Skeuomorphic Lens</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/skeuomorphism-in-fashion-trends</link>
            <description>In the wake of today's aesthetic overload, there are cowboys in Silverlake, backpackers at Target, and bike racers at lecture.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tradwife-Core And Other Aesthetic Trends Are Taking Over The Internet, But What Happens When Its Ideals Clash With Modernity?</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/tradwives-fashion-aesthetic-trend</link>
            <description>Despite homesteading content’s popularity, how many girls are really planning for a life of making bubblegum from scratch?</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Designer Eleanore Guthrie On Pioneering Knit Denim Label, Knorts, Retrospective Success, And Full Commitment </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Knorts-designer-interview</link>
            <description>The Los Angeles-based designer is able to call major celebrities such as SZA, Kylie Jenner, Camilla Cabello and more fans of her innovative designs. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2024 Venice Film Festival: 10 Standout Premieres Not To Miss</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-venice-film-festival-movies</link>
            <description>Angelina Jolie cements a cinematic return with “Maria,” and Luca Guadagnino’s latest gives “Call Me By Your Name” a run for its money.</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>“Beetlejuice Beetlejuice” and 14 Other Highly Anticipated Films Coming This September</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/september-2024-new-film-releases</link>
            <description>Jenna Ortega prepares to reveal a campy horror performance in Tim Burton’s long-awaited sequel, while Francis Ford Coppola finally releases the sci-fi epic “Megalopolis” after decades-long setbacks. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hyperpop: When Underground Internet Music Goes Mainstream</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/what-is-hyperpop</link>
            <description> Charli XCX’s club-centric record, “Brat”, brought Hyperpop to the forefront of music, and, with more music coming this fall, what exactly is it?</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Why We Can’t Get Enough of Sabrina Carpenter’s New Album “Short n’ Sweet” </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sabrina-carpenter-short-n-sweet-album-review</link>
            <description>Sabrina Carpenter’s long-awaited album, “Short n’ Sweet” is finally here, and it’s already a modern pop classic.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All The Best Shows at Swim Week Las Vegas </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Las-vegas-swim-week-2024</link>
            <description>Orchestrated by Art Hearts Fashion, over 20 designers showed and Macy Gray performed. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Rupal Banerjee On Personal Growth Through Design, And The Rise Of Fashion Label Ru By Rupal</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/ru-by-rupal-banjeree-interview</link>
            <description>The rising designer talks work and heritage behind the glowing success, and looks ahead to the brand's future.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Something Exciting is Coming August 21st!</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/The-Factory-Beyond-The-Pines</link>
            <description>Beyond The Pines Presents: The Factory </description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angel Abad</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>12 Totally “Brat” Songs From Britney Spears, Kim Petras, Slayyyter, And More</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/club-songs-similar-to-charli-xcx-brat</link>
            <description>“Brat” summer is incomplete without these essential club tracks.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>7 New Highly Anticipated Films Hitting Theaters in August 2024</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/august-2024-new-film-releases</link>
            <description>Blake Lively stars in another whirlwind romance, while Bill Skarsgård and FKA Twigs are death-defying soulmates in a new dark fantasy.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ice Spice’s Latest Album, “Y2K!” In Review</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/ice-spice-y2k-album-review</link>
            <description>With its anticipated arrival, Ice Spice’s debut album, “Y2K!,” struggles to find a sweet spot, and instead offers a look at how cultural impact can, especially in the age of a hyper-fast Internet, supersede music.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Towa Bird Talks Queer Love And Creating a New “American Hero” For Her Debut Album</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/towa-bird-american-hero-album-interview</link>
            <description>In an interview with Beyond The Pines, the rising guitarist and singer chats about tour shenanigans, writing over 100 songs, and putting lesbian representation at the forefront of her newly-released album.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How The “MaXXXine” Costume Designer Mari-An Ceo Crafted The Film’s ‘80s Aesthetic</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/maxxxine-costume-designer-fashion-interview</link>
            <description>For Ti West’s final follow up to modern day horror sensations “X” and “Pearl,” lead costume designer Mari-An Ceo immerses viewers in nostalgia while avoiding cliches at all costs.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Megan Thee Stallion: “MEGAN” Album Review</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Megan-Thee-Stallion-Megan-Album-Review</link>
            <description>On Megan Thee Stallion’s eponymous third album, the self-dubbed H-Town Hottie’s lyrics brim with Southern limericks, heated affairs, rap beef, and the rapper’s ever-adored self-confidence.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Model Alexis Ren Talks Starring in New Film &quot;Latency,&quot; Welcoming Change, And Mental Health In The Digital Age</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/alexis-ren-interview-latency-movie</link>
            <description>In conversation with BeyondThePines, Ren speaks openly about her segue into acting, launching a podcast, and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>BTP</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside The Shows At Milan And Paris Men's Fashion Week Spring/Summer 2025</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/menswear-fashion-week-2025-paris-milan</link>
            <description>Dries Van Noten exits his namesake fashion house, a debut from A$AP Rocky, and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Angela Li</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Why Charli XCX's &quot;Brat&quot; Matters Now</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/charli-xcx-brat-album</link>
            <description>“Brat,” is a bold album that reclaims The British pop star's reign, and redefines underground stardom in the present-day social media climate.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Billie Eilish: “Hit Me Hard and Soft” Album Review</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/billie-eilish-hit-me-hard-and-soft-album-review</link>
            <description>Billie Eilish’s new album opts for distinct creative choices that appear counter-intuitive to the moody, lip-pout experience the Grammy-winning singer-songwriter is known for.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All The Celebs On The AmFAR Gala Red Carpet During The 2024 Cannes Film Festival</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/amfar-gala-cannes-2024-red-carpet</link>
            <description>Beyond The Pines's Mat Abad captures the stars and fashion on the red carpet.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 8 Films Worth Seeing From The 2024 Cannes Film Festival Premieres</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-cannes-film-festival-movies</link>
            <description>Barry Keoghan and Selena Gomez earned standing ovations for “Bird” and “Emelia Pèrez” respectively, while Anya Joy-Taylor wowed in the latest installment of George Miller’s beloved action-adventure blockbuster series.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All The Best Red Carpet Fashion Moments From the 2024 Cannes Film Festival</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/best-dressed-cannes-film-festival-2024</link>
            <description>Celebrities take to the 77th Annual Cannes Film Festival in their red carpet best, celebrating the premiere of films such as Yorgos Lanthimos’s “Kinds of Kindness” and “Furiosa,” the latest installment to the Mad Max saga.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Director Jules Rosskam Explores The Trans Male Experience on Desire Lines </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/desire-lines-jules-rosskam-film-interview</link>
            <description>Jules Rosskam’s latest “hybrid” docufilm, Desire Lines, forms a thought-provoking discussion on the trans male experience using rediscovered oral histories, more contemporary interviews, and a fantasy bathhouse.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside The Making Of Sabrina Harrison’s Met Gala Look</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sabrina-harrison-met-gala-law-roach</link>
            <description>With just eight weeks to prepare, entrepreneur Sabrina Harrison enlisted the help of designer CHRISHABANA and stylists Law Roach and Carlos Alonso to make her Met Gala dreams come true.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> All The Best Celebrity Looks From the 2024 Met Gala Red Carpet </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/met-gala-2024-red-carpet-outfits</link>
            <description>The gala’s theme “The Garden of Time” honored the Costume Institute's spring exhibition, “Sleeping Beauties: Reawakening Fashion.”</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>“Challengers” Review: Guadagnino Secures Zendaya’s Leading Role Victory in a Tennis Romance</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/challengers-film-review</link>
            <description>Italian director Luca Guadagnino pulls career-best performances from Zendaya, Mike Faist, and Josh O’Connor, who are, together, entrapped in a decades-long love triangle.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How Àlex Lora Cercós Injects Politics Into His Latest Short Film “The Masterpiece”</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/alex-lora-the-masterpiece-film-interview</link>
            <description>The Award-winning director isn’t afraid to discuss the role of prejudice in international socio-political turmoil in the new short film.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All The Best Celebrity Looks of Coachella 2024</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/coachella_celebrity_style_2024</link>
            <description>From Rihanna, to Hailey Bieber and Taylor Swift, many of the biggest celebrity names brought their best fashion to the desert.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Director Tim Mielants On Navigating Grief, And Filming “Small Things Like These” With Cillian Murphy</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/tim-mielants-small-things-like-these-film-interview</link>
            <description>Tim Mielants has undeniably scored another win with his melodramatic film-adaptation of the Claire Keegan novel, spotlighting a dark time in Irish history. </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dimitra Petsa On Her Celeb-Loved Wetlook Dress, And The Unsanitized Female Experience</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/di-pesta-fashion-designer-interview</link>
            <description>The Grecian designer wants all women to celebrate their “wetness” with her emblematic Wetlook Dress, but there’s more the London-based designer wants to show the world.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Road to UEFA European Championship 2024: Brazil Clutches First Win at London Since 1995</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Brazil-wins-at-Wembley-Stadium-England-UEFA-2024</link>
            <description>17-year-old Brazilian footballer Endrick puts a stop to England’s 21-game win streak, winning 1-0 in an international friendly at Wembley Stadium ahead of summer's European Championship tournament.</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Most Anticipated Horror Films Coming In 2024</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-new-horror-movie-releases</link>
            <description>Sydney Sweeney makes her horror movie debut while this generation’s newest “scream queen,” Jenna Ortega, revamps a horror-comedy classic.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Best Red Carpet Fashion at the 2024 Oscars</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/best-dressed-oscars-2024</link>
            <description>From Chloë Sevigny in Simone Rocha to Emma Stone in Louis Vuitton</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>“Dune: Part Two”: Villeneuve Strikes Desert Gold Again</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Dune-part-2-review</link>
            <description>Timothée Chalamet and Zendaya dazzle as on-screen lovers at war in the continued Denis Villeve film adaptation of Frank Herbert’s epic sci-fi saga.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> All The Best Celebrity Moments At Paris Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/celebrity-style-paris-fashion-week-fall-winter-2024</link>
            <description>Stars such as Sydney Sweeney, Blackpink’s Jennie and Emily Ratajkowsi were dressed to the nines to attend shows.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside Casablanca’s Fall/Winter 2024 Show At Paris Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/casablanca-fall-winter-2024-runway-show</link>
            <description>The brand reimagined mythology and modern silhouettes for their new collection ‘Venus As A Boy,’ and Beyond The Pine’s Mat Abad went backstage for a closer look.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kathy Ager On The Meticulous Art Of Baroque Painting, Mortality, and Peak Consumerism</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Kathy-Ager-artist-interview</link>
            <description/>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>A Juxtaposition Of Simplicity And Over-The-Top: 7 Milan Fashion Week Shows Worth Seeing</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/milan-fashion-week-fall-winter-2024</link>
            <description>Marni returns home, Adrian Appiolaza reveals the new Moschino &amp; Diesel livestreams from behind the curtain.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>11 New Films To Keep On Your Radar For 2024</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-new-film-releases</link>
            <description>Zendaya stars in two highly anticipated films, and a new Ryan Gosling action-comedy  indicates “Barbie” wasn’t a one-off return.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> Kristen Stewart, Hunter Schafer, Adam Sandler And More Attend The 2024 Berlin Film Festival</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Berlin-film-festival-2024-photos</link>
            <description>Beyond The Pines’ Mat Abad captures the inside of the star-studded event.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris </author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Casa Cody, The Bungalow-Style Boutique Hotel In Palm Springs, Is Home Away From Home </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/casa-Cody-boutique-hotel-Palm-springs</link>
            <description>Stripped of the bells and whistles of the corporate resort, the 1920s property quietly hosts just 30 guests in bungalow-style suites, while offering reiki sessions and poolside cocktails. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Jia Foo</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For Cigarettes After Sex, Vulnerable Lyrics Are A Love Language Of Their Own</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/cigarettes-after-sex-interview-photos</link>
            <description>More than a decade into the dream pop band’s career, frontman Greg Gonzalez proves that love never dies with two previously unreleased singles.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>At New York Fashion Week, Beyonce Sat Front Row, Maximalism Is Back, And One Designer Bid The Calendar Farewell</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/new-York-fashion-week-fall-winter-2024</link>
            <description>From a Tommy Hilfiger revamp, to Peter Do’s second go at Helmut Lang, these were the shows not to be missed at New York Fashion Week.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>In Honor of Valentines Day: The Best Love Songs from Dolly Parton, Lana Del Rey and more</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/top-love-songs-valentines-day-2024</link>
            <description>15 hits for setting the mood with a loved one, or to enjoy on your own. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 2024 Sundance Films We're Still Thinking About</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sundance-film-festival-best-movies-2024</link>
            <description>The films come with star power among the likes of Pedro Pascal, Kristen Stewart, Julia Fox and Kieran Culkin.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>These Will Be The Biggest Fashion Trends Of 2024, According To The Runways</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/beyond-the-pines-2024-trends</link>
            <description>From embracing skin, to an indie sleaze update.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>See Every Film Nominated For An Academy Award At The 2024 Oscars</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-oscars-nominees-announcement</link>
            <description>Full of snubs and surprises.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Break Out Music Artists Worth Watching In 2024: Tate McRae, NewJeans, and more</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2024-break-out-emerging-music-artists</link>
            <description>New year, new(ish) faces.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Golden Globes 2024 Red Carpet Fashion: See All The Best Looks</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/golden-globes-red-carpet-2024</link>
            <description>All the best looks from Barry Keoghan in Louis Vuitton, to Rosamund Pike in Dior.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 9 Fashion Designers Set To Define 2024</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/emerging-designers-2024</link>
            <description>Already beloved gems, these designers are trailblazing their way to the forefront of the industry.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 25 Top Songs of 2023</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/best-songs-of-2023</link>
            <description>From TikTok breakouts to the latest from the world's favorite mega-stars.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside The Exhibits At Art Basel Miami 2023</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/art-basel-miami-2023</link>
            <description>Art shows were put on by entities among the likes of Louis Vuitton and Vans.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tribeca’s Talks For Tribeca Festival At Art Basel Is Open To The Public — Here’s What’s To Come</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/tribeca-talks-miami-art-basel</link>
            <description>A guide to the week, and where to purchase tickets.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Rand Al-Hadethi</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sami Miro, The Multi-Hyphenate Designer Behind The Sustainable Eponymous Denim Label, Is Defying Fashion Norms With Every Stitch</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sami-miro-designer-interview</link>
            <description>The tech professional turned fashion pioneer has carved out a space where purpose and design meet.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>&quot;Saltburn&quot; Review: A Lackluster Commentary On Privilege, Envy And Lust</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/salburn-movie-review-2023</link>
            <description>Amid outstanding performances from Barry Keoghan and Jacob Elordi, the script itself doesn't live up to director Emerald Fennell's satirical promise.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside F1 Las Vegas Grand Prix With Rihanna, Brad Pitt, Damson Idris, John Legend &amp; More</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/f1-las-vegas-grand-prix-celebrities-2023</link>
            <description>Beyond The Pine's Mat Abad (Bad Boi) captured photos of all the celebs at the star-studded race event.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Jamila Stewart</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The 21 Greatest Hip-Hop Albums of All Time, Ranked</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/best-hip-hop-albums-ranked-50th-anniversary</link>
            <description>In honor of hip-hop's 50th anniversary, we've ranked the best 21 albums from Lil Kim’s provocative “Hardcore,” to Kanye West’s “My Beautiful, Dark, Twisted Fantasy.&quot;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Phoebe Philo's Inaugural Namesake Collection Marks The Comeback Of A Generation</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/phoebe-philo-brand-collection-launch-2023</link>
            <description>The beloved designer of Celine fame is back with a line of her own after a 6-year hiatus.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Madeleine Shepherd</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Taylor Swift and Beyoncé’s Sold Out Concerts Demonstrate How Music Is Bringing Audiences Back To Theaters</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/beyonce-taylor-swift-concert-tour-films-movie-theaters</link>
            <description> Projected to boost an overall $10 billion in the U.S. economy, movie ticket sales make up a small percentage of the megastars’ influence. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Los Angeles Fashion Week Gets A Refresh</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/los-angeles-fashion-week-2023-2024</link>
            <description>Now under new ownership, the West Coast is reset with a roster of emerging designers.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paris Fashion Week Spring/Summer 2024 In Review</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/paris-fashion-week-spring-summer-2024</link>
            <description>The packed season calendar included everyone from Rick Owens to Coperni.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Best Celebrity Street Style Of Spring/Summer 2024 Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/fashion-week-2023-best-celebrity-style</link>
            <description>Beyond The Pines rounds up the best outfits from Emily Ratajkowski, Austin Butler and more</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Biggest Fashion Month Trends Place Emphasis On Wearability And Longevity</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/spring-summer-2024-fashion-trends</link>
            <description>Designers at brands such as Prada, Bottega Veneta and Gucci embrace the beauty in the everyday.</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Madeleine Shepherd</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New York Fashion Week Spring/Summer 2024 In Review: 8 Shows You May Have Missed</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/new-york-fashion-week-spring-summer-2024-recap</link>
            <description>A season of many debuts, New York Fashion Week once again goes to the emerging designer.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside Grace Ling's New York Fashion Week Debut</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/grace-ling-new-york-fashion-week-debut</link>
            <description>The Singapore-born designer's first NYFW presentation was a masterclass in performance, surrealism and illusion.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Sydney Goldhawk</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Is Music On The Brink Of A Mega Pop Revival?</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/pop-music-revival-selena-gomez-miley-cyrus-olivia-rodrigo-addison-rae</link>
            <description>New singles from Selena Gomez, Miley Cyrus, Olivia Rodrigo, and Addison Rae usher in another dance-pop renaissance, just when we thought the genre was out for good.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Andres Fabris</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How Second-Hand Shopping Became Elite, And The Conspicuous Consumption Of The Archive</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/second-hand-shopping-iding-fashion</link>
            <description>The online phenomenon begs the question: If you didn’t identify it, did you even wear it? </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The AI Diversity Paradox: Fashion's Digital Solution, Or A Superficial Gesture?</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/ai-fashion-model-diversity</link>
            <description>Brands believe artificially produced models are a revolutionary budget solution, but at what cost?</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paris Couture Week Brought Fanfare Back To The Art Form</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/haute-couture-paris-fashion-week-fall-winter-2023</link>
            <description>Schiaparelli, Jean Paul Gautier's collaboration with Paco Rabanne, and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All The Celebrities &amp; Influencers Front Row At Paris Mens Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/mens-paris-fashion-week-celebrity-influencer-photos</link>
            <description>Beyond the Pines founder Mat Abad snapped portraits of attending celebrities and influencers out and inside of the week's shows.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside Pharrell's Louis Vuitton Debut And More At Mens Paris Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/paris-fashion-week-mens-spring-summer-2024</link>
            <description>While the &quot;silent wealth&quot; trend soars, designers are again leaning into subtle statements.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Inside Naomi Campbell's 53rd Birthday Bash In Cannes</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/naomi-campbell-birthday-cannes-festival</link>
            <description>The supermodel invited friends such as Ricardo Tisci and Irina Shayk out for her big night during the 76th annual Cannes Film Festival.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Louis Pisano</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Jennie Kim of BLACKPINK's Surprise Cannes Film Festival Debut Remains One Of The Week's Best Moments</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/cannes-film-festival-the-idol-jennie-kim</link>
            <description>The K-Pop star took the carpet with Lily Rose-Depp, The Weeknd and Sam Levison ahead of the Cannes screening of The Idol.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Louis Pisano</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Return of 2010s Fashion Is Actually A Sign of the Times</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/2010s-fashion-trends-resurgence</link>
            <description>The internet hated skinnies and peplum tops, now the quintessential millennial uniform is on it's way back.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> The Next Era Of Fashion Is All About Authenticity </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/authenticity-in-fashion</link>
            <description> How some brands are getting it right. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>London Fashion Week Street Style Is Remixing Nostalgic Trends</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/london-fashion-week-street-style-spring-summer-2024</link>
            <description>10 trends influencers and editors wore throughout the week, from peplum tops to ballet flats.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Madeleine Shepherd</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>10 Fashion Trends Shaping The Fall/Winter 2023 Season</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/fashion-week-trends-fall-winter-2023</link>
            <description>Women in neckties, tiny bras, and all.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Joyce Onuorah</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paris Fashion Week Fall/Winter 2023: Technology and Sensibility</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/paris-fashion-week-fall-winter-2023</link>
            <description>Unpacking Coperni, Saint Laurent and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>At Milan Fashion Week, Trendiness And Practicality Reach A Crossroads</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/milan-fashion-week-fall-2023</link>
            <description>Legacy houses usher in the wave of new minimalism.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Joyce Onuorah</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Emerging Designers Won New York Fashion Week</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/new-york-fashion-week-emerging-designers-fall-2023</link>
            <description>Some designers basked in the conceptual, while others signaled a return to a more practical way of dressing ahead. </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Haider Ackermann’s Jean Paul Gaultier Couture Presentation Is An Authentic Merging Of The Best Of Both Worlds</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/jean-paul-gaultier-haider-ackermann-couture-2023</link>
            <description>The designer invoked suiting, corsetry, and manipulation of metal to reinterpret Gaultier's classic designs.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mugler's Return To The Runway Was A Love Letter To Theatrics </title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/mugler-fall-2023-runway</link>
            <description>Alongside gothic lace and corsets, the show itself was a triumph of technological innovation. </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Jailynn Taylor</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mens Fall 2023 Was A Fashion Week To Watch – Breaking Down 6 Of The Shows</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/menswear-fall-2023-fashion-week</link>
            <description>Colm Dillane of KidSuper co-designs Louis Vuitton's latest menswear collection, Dior dabbles in minimalism, and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Boys In Briefs, And More – Inside Loewe's Take On Minimalism</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/loewe-mens-fall-2023-runway</link>
            <description>The brand's Fall 2023 mens collection merges the incoming minimalism wave with JW Anderson's signature playfulness.</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Alexandra Hildreth</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sumire</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/sumire</link>
            <description>Sumire is a 'Japanese American gal living in Tokyo.' She smolders for the camera and shares her life's greatest teachers, lessons, and more..  </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Photography</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Gucci x Dickies: Artisan Workwear like we've never seen before</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/gucci_dickies</link>
            <description>A limited selection of Dickies workwear becomes extra precious by entering the hands of Gucci’s artisans, who embellish each piece stud by stud, crystal by crystal, to create unique forms of shining self-expression.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Watch: The second chapter of Louis Vuitton's Men’s Pre-Spring 2023</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/LV_mens_s23</link>
            <description>Constructing a coming-of-age silhouette, the #LouisVuitton Collection is presented as an evolution in a man’s wardrobe.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Muse Interview with Isabella Kroon</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/muse_interview_isabella_kroon</link>
            <description>Fresh face Vol. 3 muse, Isabella Kroon shares her thoughts on her favorite winter wardrobe pieces. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Watch: An inside look at the Dior Men Fall 2023 runway</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/Dior_fall_2023</link>
            <description>The unveiling of the collection by Kim Jones at the monumental Giza pyramid complex in Egypt.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The opening of ‘Niketown’ in New York, November 1996</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/niketown</link>
            <description/>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How we produced our 100% recycled bottle cap beanies</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/beanies</link>
            <description>Supersoft and super sustainable. Enabling the utilization of recycled materials in place of new material with merely a small change to the processing method. </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Patricia Velasquez by Marc Hispard, 1993</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/PatriciaVelasquez-MarcHispard1993</link>
            <description/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Giving Tuesday Reflection</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/giving_tuesday_2022</link>
            <description>At the center of our efforts is humanitarianism. Your subscriptions and purchases of products helps improve lives by empowering communities worldwide.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Muse Interview with Cece Rose</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/muse_interview_cece_rose</link>
            <description>Fresh face Vol. 3 muse, Cece Rose shares what her booking experience  with us was like and dishes on the one article of clothing she basically exclusively exists in. Watch more from her video interview. </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Brand Merchandise: Sustainably sourced and handcrafted in japan and peru</title>
            <link>https://www.beyondthepines.com/blogs/nov_merch</link>
            <description>Beyond the Pines is not identified with a single product family, but evokes a broad spectrum of values and meanings.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
            <author>Ash Alanis</author>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
